[{"answer": "Well, the Republicans are just in a dither over what Todd Akin said.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "What do you think is going on here?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Well, and we'll find out some more tomorrow because the Republican Platform Committee is going to have a vote on whether or not the human life amendment, which would ban most -- almost all abortions, I believe only maybe the life of the mother would be an exception.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "And if you're looking at this from the outside, you're saying, well, what do these guys really believe?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Yes, we could have asked for a better story.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Margaret, this is a real mess, isn't it?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Well, you know, perhaps they will.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "I mean if they believe that, why don't they just say it?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "I mean --", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Yes, he's not Mitt Romney, isn't he?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well, Piers --", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "So how can he -- how can he use this issue to drive people out of office?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, what is interesting is that the platform committee votes for it.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "So, again where is his credibility on this?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Well, certainly Republicans don't like talking about social issues.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "This is the very last thing that Mitt Romney wanted to blow up, isn't it?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Well, nobody can make him go.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Why isn't he gone yet?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know about the semantics of it.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Have you any idea?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "ILVER: I think the problem is that people's imagination might almost be worse with all the different possibilities of what it could be.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "What do you have to say?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "I mean I think yes.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Ben, very quickly on the tax, do you think he should release more?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, my reaction is to not talk publicly about it.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "What is your reaction to this?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "It's disappointing.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Do you find it odd that we're still even debating this in 2012?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "For example, last week, we did a show on hormones.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "What kind of thing are you going to be really getting into from a personal point of view?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "I'm not nervous from the standpoint I have done it before.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "How you feeling?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "You know, I have a feeling I did.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Did you ever meet her?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I think for me, it's being true to myself.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "What is the secret to getting over the low parts?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "It's pretty much stayed the same.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "How have things moved on since then?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "This is what your kind of viewers are going through on a daily basis, isn't it?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Can I help you?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "You have already?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Does she know really what brought this on?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Only 165,000.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "How many Twitter followers do you have now?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "I'm glad you asked.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "How about you, Piers?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "I don't really see -- people, thank goodness, have been really nice to me.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "But when people are really nasty or vicious, how do you deal with that?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Can you do anything about that?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Ricki lake.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "What's your address?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Well, there's absolutely no evidence, and I mean no evidence that he was anywhere near Kathy Savio's house that date that she died.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Why are you so convinced of your client's innocence?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Well, not really when you look at it.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "It was a pretty strange set of facts if it doesn't involve homicide, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "First, I thought that Rob Lowe looked more like the state's attorney, Jim Glasgow, than he did like Drew.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "If so, what did you think of it?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "The only -- to some extent it does.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "Does it matter in a criminal case?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "I mean, Stacey Peterson is an ongoing investigation.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Do you have any theories yourself about what happened to Stacey Peterson?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "He's actually a very down to Earth guy, a very personable guy.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "What kind of guy is he when there are no cameras around and he's not showing off a bit?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "I know who's not going to be a member.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "What are they going to do?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "You.", "docId": "120820pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Who, me?", "qSentId": 665}]